https://felineinstincts.com/returns-and-refunds-policy/

Ordering InformationHoliday Shipping InformationShipping Cost NoticeLegal & PrivacyInternational OrdersAttn: China CustomersReturns, Refunds, and Privacy PolicyFAQContact UsSite-MapShopCartMy AccountCheckout 0 Items
Returns, Refunds, and Privacy Policy Cancellations, Returns and Refunds: We have to refuse the return of any product because do not replace items back for resale once sold.If you need to cancel your order for any reason, please contact us the same day you ordered to assure we do not proceed with shipping. If we have already shipped your order you may refuse delivery from the U.S. Post Office or FedEx and the order will be returned to us. Once the package is received back at our warehouse in good order, we will contact you and process your refund. A handling charge of between $5-$10 will apply on these and other returns and will be based on the size of the original order. Shipping fees and credit card fees are NOT refundablePlease make sure you make an informed purchase. Any pet food or supplement sold in our store is a FINAL SALE. For quality control reasons we do not re-sell  items returned to us. We cannot accept returns for the following reasons:Customer changed their mind and no longer wants the product.Customer thought product was something else.Customer’s pet(s) did not eat product.Customer’s pet appears to have intolerance to product.Customer wishes to exchange product after allowing it to expireThe vet said to not feed rawPrivacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://felineinstincts.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsWhen you submit information through one of our contact forms, your entries are stored in our system in order to contact you. This information is used solely by us and is not provided to any third parties. Contact information provided on contact forms may be used to provide you with additional information on our products and services via email, phone, or direct mail.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsIn order to improve the performance of our site and make beneficial to the most users, an anonymized string of data may be passed to analytics tracking services such as Google. The information used for analytics does not contain any personal identifying information, but does provide a general location, pages visited, referring site information, and the type of device use to access the site.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Additional informationWhat data breach procedures we have in placeIn the event of a minor data breach where no personal information is effected, we will alert the appropriate authorities and enhance security to prevent similar breaches.. Should a major data breach occur where your personal information may be compromised, we will alert you at the earliest possible time in order for you to change your passwords and take any necessary precautions.
Cart My Natural Cat Book Order the book in in the shopping menu.  For more information on Felice Arata´s new book visit: www.mynaturalcats.com
